我从未认真想过我会如何死去
I'd never given much thought to how I would die.
但是为我爱的人而死似乎是个不错的选择
But dying in the place of someone I love seems like a good way to go.
所以我并不后悔当初离开家的决定
So, I can't bring myself to regret the decision to leave home.
我会想念我挚爱的那个粗心大意、稳定性奇差的母亲和她的新丈夫
I would miss my loving, erratic, harebrained mother and her new husband.
这应该是件好事 我是这么想的
this will be a good thing,I think.
人口数只有 3,120人
Population: 3120 people.
那正是我要搬去的地方
This is where I'm moving
我的父亲是查理
My dad's Charlie.
他是这里的警长
He's the Chief of Police.
你的头发变长了
Your hair's longer.
上次见你之后我剪过了
I cut since last time I saw you.
我猜它大概长得挺快的吧
I guess it grew a lot again.
每年夏天，我都会来这里住两个礼拜左右
I used to spend two weeks here almost every summer,
但那已经是多年前的事了...
But it's been years...
我把浴室的架子清理干净了
I cleared some shelves up in the bathroom.
哦，好的
Oh, right
一间浴室
One bathroom.
蛮实用的工作台灯
It's a pretty good work lamp.
席尔斯的销售小姐帮我选的床组
The Sears lady picked up the bed stuff.
你喜欢紫色，对吧？
You like purple, right?
紫色很正点
Purple's cool.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Okay.
查理最大的优点之一就是...
One of the best things about Charlie...
他不会啰嗦
He doesn't hover.
我听说你们一路赶过来
I heard you guys coming all the way down the road.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
贝拉，你还记得比利．布雷克吗？
Bella, you remember Billy Black?
记得
Yeah.
你气色看来不错
You're looking good.
我还有持续在练舞呢
I'm still dancing.
我很高兴你终于来了
I'm glad you are finally here.
听说你要来，查理就一直说个不停
Charlie here hasn't shut up about it since you told him you were coming.
好啦，少在那夸张了，小心我拖你去喂泥巴
Alright, keep exaggerating,I'll roll you into the mud
你敢我就辗你的脚丫子
Until I ram you in the ankles.
好，来啊！
Yeah, bring it!
嗨，我是雅各布
Hi, I'm Jacob.
我们小时候经常一起玩泥巴作成派
We used to make mud pies when we were little.
对，我还记得
Right, I remember.
他们经常这样闹吗？
Are they always like this?
越老越严重
It's getting worse with old age.
所以，你觉得如何？
So, what do you think?
什么？
What?
你回家的礼物
Your homecoming present.
这个吗？
This?
刚向比利买来的
Just bought it off Billy.
没错
Yep.
我帮你重新整修了引擎
I totally rebuilt the engine for you.
喔，老天
Oh God
不会吧，哦，我的天啊！
Come on.Oh My Gosh!
这真是太棒了！
This is perfect!
这不是开玩笑吧 !
You must be joking!
抱歉
Sorry.
我就说她会喜欢的
I told you she'd love it.
我最懂得怎么安抚小孩子了
I'm down with the kids.
是阿，老兄，你就是个爱吹嘘的家伙
Oh, yeah dude. You're the bomb.
好吧
Okay,
你换挡的时候要踩两下离合器
You gotta double pump the clutch when you shift
除了这个，你应该没什么问题的
Besides that, you should be good.
是这个吗？
That's this one?
对，就是那个
Yeah, right there.
好的
Alright.
你要搭便车去学校吗 ?
You want a ride to school or something?
我上的是保留区里的学校
I go to school on the reservation.
哦，好吧
Oh, right.
太糟了，我好不容易才有个认识的人
That's too bad. It would've been good to know one person.
我到新学校的第一天
My first day in a new school.
那是三月，正好是学期中
It's March, the middle of the semester.
好极了
Great.
车不错
Nice ride.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是伊莎贝拉 史旺，新来的女生
You're Isabella Swan, the new girl.
嗨 ! 我叫艾瑞克，我是本地的万事通
Hi! I'm Eric, the eyes and ears of this place.
你需要什么协助吗？导游、餐饮伙伴...
Anything you need? Tour guide,lunch date...
诉苦的对象
A shoulder to cry on.
我是校刊社的，而你是本校的新闻了，宝贝
I'm on the paper and you're news baby,
喔，我不是..
Oh,I am not..
拜托别这样...
Please don't...
喔喔 ! 别紧张
Whoa! Relax.
好...谢了
Okay...thanks.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不，不是...那是...
No, no...That's...
你是伊莎贝拉，对吧 ?
You're Isabella, right?
是啦，嗨！我是麦克...纽顿
Yeah, hey! I'm Mike... Newton.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
她让你碰了个大钉子，哈 ?
She's got a great spike, huh?
顺便说一下，我叫洁西卡
I'm Jessica, by the way.
嘿，你从亚利桑那州来的对吧？
Hey, you're from Arizona, right?
对
Yeah.
亚利桑那州的人不都是...小麦肤色吗？
Aren't people from Arizona supposed to be like...really tan?
是啊，这大概就是我被他们踢出来的原因吧
Yeah, maybe that's why they kicked me out.
你好样的
You're good.
很有趣
That's so funny
一件杰出的事 ...
A Master Piece...
嗨，麦克！见见我邻家的女孩，贝拉
Hey Mikey! You met my home girl, Bella.
喔，你的邻家女孩？
Oh, your home girl?
对啊
Yeah.
我的女孩
My girl
泰勒
Tyler.
喔，天哪
Oh my God,
真像是又回到一年级的幼稚模样
it's like first grade all over again.
你就像是最闪亮的新玩具
You're the shiny new toy.
笑一个！
Smile!
好...
Okay...
好吧，我只是..
It's okay, I just...
我挺你，宝贝
I got your back, baby.
我想将讨论的方向转为青少年酗酒
I guess we'll just turn another editorial on teen drinking.
其实你可以讨论...暴饮暴食... 游泳队的竞速计划 ....
You can always go for...The eating disorders...Speedo padding on the swim team...
说真的，这个点子不错
Actually, that's a good one.
是啊，对，我就是这么想的
Yeah, right. That's exactly what I thought.
我们是在讨论奥林匹克的规格了
We're talking Olympic size.
那是不可能的，他太瘦了，太不协调了
There's no way, he's so skinny.It doesn't make sense.
绝对
Totally
他们是谁？
Who are they?
库伦家族
The Cullens.
他们 呃...
They're, um...
库伦医生夫妇领养的孩子
Dr. and Mrs. Cullen foster kids.
几年前他们从阿拉斯加搬来这儿
They moved down here from Alaska a few years ago.
他们只和自己人相处
They kind of keep to themselves.
对，因为他们都同进同出
Yeah, 'cause they're all together.
就像是双双对对
Like together together.
那个金发的女孩叫罗丝莉 而那个大个子的黑发男生是艾密特
The blond girl, that's Rosalie,and the big dark-haired guy, Emmett.
看起来还真像是情侣
They're like a thing.
洁西，他们没有血缘关系
Jess, they're not actually related.
对啊，但他们竟然住一起...这太怪了
Yeah, but they live together...It's weird.
那个身材娇小的黑发女生叫艾莉丝
The little dark-haired girl is Alice.
她才真诡异呢
She's really weird.
还有...她与贾斯柏是一对，金发的那个 他看起来好像生病似的
And...She's with Jasper, the blonde one,who looks like he's in pain.
库伦医生就像个婚姻中介所的养父
Dr.Cullen is like this foster dad-slash-match maker.
也许他会收养我
Maybe he'll adopt me.
这又是谁 ?
Who's he?
他是...爱德华库伦
That's...Edward Cullen.
很明显的，他倒是挺迷人的
He's totally gorgeous, obviously.
但更明显的是，这儿还没有能与他匹配的人
But apparently nobody here is good enough for him.
所以... 呃 ....
So...Yeah...
说真的，你可别浪费时间去...
Seriously, don't waste your time...
我才没那个兴趣
I wasn't planning on it.
莫利纳先生 ?
Mr. Molina ?
嗨，麦克
Hey, Mike.
喔，好的...史旺小姐
Oh, yes... Ms.Swan.
这是你的讲义，好吗 ?
Here's your stuff, okay?
还有...我帮你在这安排了个位子
And...I got a seat for you right here
是在最后一个 所以...
it's the last one so...
跟紧点，你会跟上进度的
Just tag along until you catch up.
好了，同学们，今天我们要观察涡虫的行为
Alright guys, today we're gonna be observing the behavior of Planaria,
物理？生物化学？
Physics? Biochem?
每个课程人数都额满了，亲爱的
Every class is full, my dear.
我刚刚查过了
I just checked in here.
恐怕你只能继续上生物课了
I'm afraid you'll have to stay in Biology.
好吧，我只能...试着去忍受了
Fine, I'll just...accept to endure it.
我只是还不能习惯你已经长这么大了 而且还这么漂亮
I just can't get over how grown up you are.And so gorgeous.
嗨，贝拉 !
Hey, Bella!
你还记得我吗？
You remember me?
有一年我扮圣诞老人..
I played Santa one year...
是阿，维隆，她四岁以后就没在这里过圣诞节了
Yeah, Waylon.She hasn't had a Christmas here since she was four.
我打赌我给你留下印象了，不是吗？
I bet I made an impression, didn't I?
你一直都是这样的
You always do.
露股沟的圣诞老人
Bad crack Santa.
嘿，但是孩子们可喜欢那些小瓶子了
Hey! Kids love those little bottles though.
维隆，你让她好好的享受花园汉堡吧
Let the girl eat her Garden Burger, Waylon.
等你吃完后，我会尽快送来你最爱的..
As soon as you done I will bring you your favorite...
草莓馅饼，记得吗？
Berry Cobbler, remember?
太棒了，谢谢你
Thank you, that will be great.
嘿，宝贝，听着
Hey baby! So listen,
假如费尔的训练结束了
if Phil's training goes well,
我们可能搬到佛罗里达
we could be moving to Florida.
妈妈，你的手机呢 ？
Mom, where's your cel?
好吧，不准笑
Okay, don't laugh.
我的充电器没有掉，只是它跑走了
I didn't lose my power cord, it ran away.
笑死人了
Screaming.
我现在渐渐讨厌高科技了
I literally repel technology now.
我很想你
I miss you.
喔，宝贝！我也很想你
Oh, Baby! I miss you too.
告诉我些你学校的事吧...那里的孩子怎么样？
But tell me more about your school...What are the kids like?
有没有可爱的男生 ?
Are there any cute guys?
他们对你好吗？
Are they being nice to you?
呃...他们都很"欢迎"我
Well...They're all very welcoming.
喔哦，都说来听听吧
Uh-oh. Tell me all about it.
也没什么重要的
It doesn't even matter.
可是我要做作业了
I have homework to do.
我晚点打给你吧
I'll talk to you later.
好吧，我爱你
Okay, I love you.
我也爱你
Love you too.
我打算直接面对他
I planned to confront him.
去搞清楚他到底有什么毛病
And demand to know what his problem was.
但他没再出现了
But he never showed.
贝拉！
Bella!
过了一天...
And the next day...
还是没出现
Another no-show.
几天过去了
More days passed.
事情似乎变得有点... 怪怪的
And things were getting a little...Strange.
你没事吧？
Are you alright?
是，我没事
Yeah, I'm good.
地上结冰后就无法止滑
Ice doesn't really help the uncoordinated.
对啊，所以我帮你的卡车换上新轮胎了
Yeah,that's why I had some new tires put on the truck.
旧的轮胎表面已经磨平了
The old ones were getting really bold.
嗯， 我可能来不及回来吃晚餐了
Well, I'll probably be late for dinner.
我必须赶到梅森郡
Gotta head down to Mason County.
有个杰里逊面粉厂的警卫，不知道被甚么野兽咬死了
A security guard at the Grisham mill got killed by some kind of animal.
总之，我打算增加人手
Anyway, I figured I'd lend a hand.
小心点
Be careful.
我一向都如此
Always am.
谢谢你帮我换轮胎
And thanks for the tires.
没什么
Yeah.
舞会委员就像是个乌合之众
Prom Committee is a chick thing ,
但我帮他们把文宣的部分搞定了
but I got it covered for the paper anyway,
我需要你的播放清单
I need your playlist.
嘿！听好，我在想...
Hey! Listen, I was wondering...
嗯，你是否已经有约...
Um, Did you have a date to the...
你会渐渐适应的
You gotta get used to it.
嘿，麦克，你真好笑
Hey Mike, you're real cute man.
哦，不 ...
Oh, no...
你好
Hello.
我很抱歉，上个礼拜没机会自我介绍
I'm sorry I didn't get the chance to introduce myself last week.
我是爱德华 库伦
I'm Edward Cullen.
你叫贝拉 ?
You're Bella?
对
Yes.
洋葱根端细胞 !
Onion root tip cells!
把它分开，并且将不同的分裂阶段记下来
So separate and label them into the phases of Mitosis.
第一对完成的会拿到这个奖品
And the first partners to get it right are gonna win.
金洋葱！
The golden onion!
女士优先
Ladies first...
是的，我出城了几天
Yeah. I was out of town for a couple of days.
私人原因
Personal reasons.
初期
Prophase.
你介意... 我看一下吗？
You mind if I... look?
是初期
It's prophase.
我就说了吧
Like I said.
那么...你喜欢下雨天吗?
So... You're enjoying the rain?
什么？
What?
你是在问我天气吗？
You're asking me about the weather?
是啊 ...
Yeah...
我想是吧
I guess I am.
其实，我不太喜欢下雨
Well, I don't really like the rain.
而且我真的...
And I'm really...
什么？
What?
没事
Nothing.
这是...后期
It's... Anaphase
介意我检查一下吗？
You mind if I check?
当然不介意
Sure.
后期
Anaphase.
我就说了吧
Like I said.
你怎会想搬来全美最潮湿的地方呢？
why did you move to wettest place in the continental U.S.?
这说来很复杂
It's complicated.
呃，我妈妈再婚了而且...
Um, my mom remarried and...
所以你不喜欢那个男的？
So, you don't like the guy?
不，不是那样的...费尔人不错
No, that's not...Phil's really nice.
中期，你要检查吗？
It's Metaphase.  You wanna check it?
不了，我相信你
No, I believe you.
你怎么不跟你妈妈和费尔住 ?
Why didn't you move with your mother and Phil?
呃，费尔是小联盟的棒球员
Well, Phil's a minor league baseball player.
我妈妈待在家陪我
My mom stayed home with me
我想我应该和我爸住一段时间...
I figured I'd stay with my dad for a while...
抱歉，我只是想试着了解你
I'm sorry, I'm just trying to figure you out.
你对我来说很难看透
You're very difficult for me to read.
你戴隐形眼镜吗？
did you get contacts?
没有
No.
上次我看见你时，你的眼睛是黑色的，可是现在...是金棕色了
Your eyes were black the last time I saw you and now...They're like golden-brown.
对，我知道，那是 ... 呃...是荧光效应
Yeah, I know. It's the... Um...it's the fluorescence.
贝拉，真的很抱歉 ....我吓坏了
Bella, I'm so sorry... I panicked.
贝拉
Bella
你没事吧？
are you okay?
你给我好好说清楚
You and I are gonna talk.
你没事吧？
You alright ?
爸，我没事，冷静点
I'm fine dad, calm down.
我真的很对不起你，贝拉，我煞不住车
I'm sorry Bella, I tried to stop.
我知道，没关系
I know, it's okay.
不，混蛋，我很确定那很不好
No, as sure as hell it's not okay.
爸，他不是故意的
Dad, it wasn't his fault.
你差点没命了，你知道吗？
You could've been killed. You understand that?
是的，可是我没有，所以 ...
Yes. But I wasn't, so...
你可以和你的驾照吻别了！
You can kiss your license goodbye.
我听说警长的女儿在这儿
I heard the Chief's daughter was in.
喔，库伦医师
Oh, Dr.Cullen.
查理
Charlie.
交给我吧，杰克
I got this one, Jackie.
伊莎贝拉
Isabella.
贝拉
Bella.
好的，贝拉，这看起来是轻微摔伤
Well, Bella. Looks like it's a quiet spill.
很好
Good.
看这里
Look here.
你可能处于创伤后压力症候群
You might experience some post-traumatic stress.
我认为你应该没事
I think you'll be just fine.
贝拉，我真的很抱歉，我实在是...
I'm so sorry Bella, I'm really...
幸好爱德华正在那里，不然我就惨了
It would have been a lot worse if Edward wasn't there.
他及时把我推开了
He knocked me out of the way.
爱德华？你的孩子 ?
Edward? Your boy?
是的，那真是令人惊讶
Yeah, it was amazing.
我意思是，他突然出现在我身边
I mean, he got to me so fast.
看来你运气很好
Sounds like you were very lucky.
查理
Charlie
我还有些文件要处理
I need to sign some paperwork.
你该给你妈打电话
You should probably call your mom.
你告诉她了？
Did you tell her?
她恐怕早已...吓坏了
She's probably just...freaking out.
不然我该做什么？让她死吗 ?
What was I supposed to do?Let her die?
这不只是你的事
This isn't just about you.
我觉得我们应该到我的办公室谈...
I think we should talk this in my office...
我能和你谈谈吗？
Can I talk to you for a minute?
罗丝莉...
Rosalie...
什么事？
What?
你...你怎么能那么快就来到我身边 ?
How...how did you get over to me so fast?
我当时就站在你的身边啊，贝拉
I was standing right next to you, Bella.
不
No
你是站在你的车旁边...离我很远
you were next to your car... Across the lot.
不，我没有
No, I wasn't.
是，你确实是这样的 !
Yes, you were!
贝拉，你撞到了头...我想你有点精神错乱了
Bella, you hit your head... I think you're confused.
我很清楚我看见了什么
I know what I saw.
那究竟是怎么回事 ?
What exactly was that?
你...你把车子挡下来了
You...You stopped the van.
你用手把它推开了
You pushed it away with your hand.
呃，我想没有人会相信你说的，所以...
Well, nobody's gonna believe you, so...
我不会告诉任何人的
I wasn't gonna tell anybody.
我只想知道...真相
I just need to know...the truth.
你就不能谢谢我然后忘了这件事吗？
Can't you just thank me and get over it?
谢谢你
Thank you.
你不能让这件事就这么过去吗 ?
You're not gonna let this go, are you?
不能
No
那好吧，我想你会尽情享受失望的
Well, then I hope you enjoy disappointment.
那是我第一次梦见爱德华 库伦
That was the first night I dreamt with Edward Cullen.
每个人把通行证拿出来，所以...
I need everybody's permission slips, so...
走吧
Let's go
看看你，哼 ?
Look at you, huh?
你还活着！
You're alive!
我知道，是啊...我猜是个假警报
I know, Yeah... False alarm, I guess.
嗯，我想问你，你知道的...
Um, now I wanted to ask you, you know...
你想去...舞会吗？
Do you wanna go to Prom...?
所以...你觉得呢？
So... What do you think?
关于什么？
About what?
对我来说不是好主意
Not such a good idea for me.
无论如何，那个周末我有事
I have something that weekend, anyway.
我刚好那个周末要去杰克逊维州
I'm going to Jacksonville that weekend.
你不能在另一个周末去吗？
You can't go another weekend?
不能退的车票
Non-refundable ticket.
你应该去邀请洁西卡的
You should ask Jessica.
我知道她想和你一起去
I know she wants to go with you.
呦，呦，呦
Yo, yo, yo
嘿，大伙们！
hey guys!
好！出发吧！
Good! Let's go!
蛋壳，胡萝卜叶端..
Eggshells, carrot-tops...
很棒，很棒
Very good, very good.
现在我要做一杯热腾腾的堆肥茶
Now I'm gonna make a steaming cup of compost-tea.
给我..
Give me that..
那个不能喝啦！那是给植物喝的...
Don't drink it! It's for the plants...
去杰克逊维州做什么呢 ?
What's in Jacksonville?
你怎么知道的?
How did you know about that?
我...你没回答我的问题
I...You didn't answer my question.
这个嘛，你也没回答过我的问题，所以...
Well, you don't answer any of mine, so...
嗨
Hi
你愿意告诉我，你是怎么挡住车子的吗 ?
Are you gonna tell me how you stopped the van?
是啊...我的肾上腺素上升
Yeah...I had an adrenaline rush.
那很正常
It's very common.
你可以上谷歌查
You can Google it.
佛罗里达人...
Floridians...
听我说... 我很抱歉一直都不太有礼貌
Look... I'm sorry I'm being rude all the time.
我只是认为这样是最好的方式
I just think it's the best way.
贝拉！猜猜谁约我去舞会
Bella! Guess who's just asked me to Prom.
呃，你不觉得这有点奇怪吗 ?
Um, it's not gonna be weird though, right?
不会，一点都不奇怪
No, zero weirdness.
大伙儿都在，真好
You guys are great together.
贝拉，你看
Bella, look.
一条虫...一条虫...
It's a worm... It's a worm...
贝拉...我们不应该做朋友的
Bella...We shouldn't be friends.
我意思是，你当初为什么不让车子压扁我 ？
I mean, why didn't you just let the van crush me?
你认为我后悔救了你？
You think I regret saving you?
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything.
不，我们的巴士坐满了
No, our bus is full.
你妈妈又...打来了
Your mom called...Again.
好吧，都怪你
Well, that's your fault.
你不该告诉她这件小意外的
You shouldn't have told her about the almost-accident.
你吃完了吗？
Are you finished?
是的
Yeah.
她似乎跟以前不太一样
She seems different.
费尔听起来像是个不错的男人
Phil sounds like an alright guy.
是阿，他是不错
Yeah, he is.
好吧...
Alright...
那代表什么意思 ?
Should I know what that means?
那边还有鲸鱼可以看呢，和我们一起去吧
But there's whale watching too. Come with us.
贝拉
Bella.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道吗，你的态度反反复覆真令人难以捉摸
You know, your mood swings are kind of giving me a whiplash.
我只说我们不做朋友会比较好 但那不是我所想要的
I only said it'd be better for you if we weren't friends,not that I didn't want to be.
那是什么意思 ？
What does that mean?
意思是你够聪明的话，应该离我远些
It means, if you're smart, you'd stay away from me.
你愿意告诉我真相吗 ?
Will you tell me truth?
不，可能不会
No, probably not.
我宁可听听你的理论
I'd rather hear your theories.
都是些超级英雄，对吗？
That's all super-hero stuff, right?
那如果我不是英雄呢？
What if I'm not the hero?
如果我是... 坏人呢？
What if I'm...the bad guy?
你不是的
You're not.
我能理解你为何想推拖
I can see what you're trying to put off.
不如我们... 一起聚会 ?
Why don't we just...hang out?
大家都要去海边
Everybody is going to the beach.
一起来吧
Come
我的意思是，很好玩
I mean, have fun.
哪个海滩？
Which beach?
我不知道
I don't know.
那个海滩有什么不好吗？
Is there something wrong with that beach?
只是有点拥挤
It's just a little crowded.
冷死了
Its freezing.
你应该出来走走的，伙计
You gotta go out, folks.
我都不知道是否值得这么做
I don't know if it's worth it anymore.
所以我一直期待艾瑞克邀请我去舞会
So, I keep thinking that Eric's gonna ask me to the Prom
但...他却没有
And he just...doesn't.
你应该去邀请他
You should ask him.
主动点，你是个独立的女强人
Take control. You are a strong independent woman.
我是吗？
I am?
是的
Yes.
你能帮帮我吗？
Can you help me out?
好啊
Yeah.
贝拉！
Bella!
嗨，雅各布！大伙们，这是雅各布
Hi Jacob!Guys, this is Jacob.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
你想干嘛，跟踪我吗？
What are you, like, stalking me?
你可是在我的地盘呢，记得吗？
You're on my rez, remember?
你冲浪吗 ?
Are you surfing?
当然不是
Definitely not.
你们应该陪陪贝拉
You guys should keep Bella company.
呃，她的约会泡汤了
Um,her date bailed.
什么约会？
What date?
她邀请了爱德华
She invited Edward.
只是出于礼貌而已
To be polite, that's it.
我觉得她不错，敢去约爱德华，没有人试过
I think it's nice she invited him.Nobody ever does.
是啊，因为库伦家都是怪胎
Yeah, 'cause Cullen's a freak.
你还真说对了 !
You got that right!
你们认识他？
You guys know him?
库伦家族不会来这里的
The Cullens don't come here.
你听到了，呃?
You caught that, huh?
我不该说任何关于这件事的
I'm not really supposed to say anything about it.
嘿，我会保密的
Hey, I can keep a secret.
呃，这就像是个古老的恐怖故事
Um, really it's just like an old scary story.
好，我想知道
Well, I want to know.
什么？
What?
像狼...真的野狼？
Like wolves... Real wolves?
是的...其实那就是我们部族的传说
Yeah...That's a legend of our tribe.
好吧，那这个跟库伦家族有什么关系 ?
Okay. So, what's the story about the Cullens?
我的曾祖父，酋长，曾发现他们在我们的土地狩猎
My great-grandfather, the chief,found them hunting on our land.
但他们自认为是异类，所以我们就缔结了约定
But they claimed to be something different, so we made a treaty with them.
如果他们不踏入库利特斯这片领地
If they promised to say off Quileute lands,
那我们也不会泄露他们真正的身份... 给白种人知道
Then we wouldn't expose what they really were...to the pale faces.
我以为他们才刚搬来这
I thought they just moved here.
那他们到底是什么东西？
What are they really?
这只是个故事，贝拉
It's just a story, Bella.
来吧，我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
我妈妈说我不会哄小猫叫...
My mamma said I didn't know how to make a kitten meow...
你好？
Hello?
小妞？
Girl?
小妞！
Girl!
你好
Hello.
外套很好看
Nice jacket.
你是谁？
Who are you?
总是千篇一律的蠢问题
It's always the same inane questions.
詹姆斯...
James...
别再戏弄我们的食物了
Let's not play with our food.
他不在这里
He's not here.
每当天气好的时候，库伦家族就消失了
Whenever the weather's nice the Cullens disappear.
不，库伦夫妇会带着他们去旅行、露营、吃东西
No, Dr. and Mrs. Cullen yank them out for hiking and camping and stuff.
我邀请他...我采取主动了
I just asked him... I took control.
我就说过这会管用的
I told you that would happen.
哦，是的，家里的一些杂事要处理
Oh, yeah. It's a weird family thing.
好吧，我们该去安吉拉斯港购物了 免得被别人抢先买光了
Okay, we should go shopping to Port Angeles before all the good dresses get cleaned out.
安吉拉斯港？
Port Angeles?
你们介意我去吗？
You mind if I come?
我喜欢这件
I like this one
很正点
That's cool.
但是我搞不懂这种细肩带的
But I don't know about the one-shoulder thing
我喜欢这件
I like this one.
对，我喜欢这种编织
Yeah, I like the knitting.
洁西，你觉得怎么样？熏衣草色？
Jess, what do you think? Lavender?
那个好吗 ? 颜色适合我吗 ?
Is that good? Is that my color?
我喜欢，我偏好暗玫瑰色这件
I like it. I like that dusty-rose one too.
喔，我喜欢这件 ...
Okay, I like this one...
那感觉满不舒服的
That is uncomfortable.
呃，蛮恶心的...
Oh, it's disgusting...
贝拉，你觉得怎么样？
Bella, what do you think?
看起来不错
Looks great.
前五件礼服，你都说一样的话耶
You said that about the last five dresses though.
我觉得都很不错啊
I thought they were pretty good.
你对这不感兴趣，对吗？
Not really into this, are you?
其实，我只是想去书店
I, actually, really just wanna go to this bookstore.
那我们在餐厅见吧 ?
Meet you guys at the restaurant?
你确定？
Are you sure?
嗯，待会见
Yeah, see you in a minute.
好的
Okay.
好
晚安
Good night.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们在服饰店见过
We saw you at the dress shop.
嘿，你要去哪里？
Hey, where are you running to?
她在这呢…
There she is...
大家好吗 ?
How are you guys doing?
怎么了，小妞 ?
What's up, girl?
哇!你要去哪？
Whoa! Where are you going?
你要去哪？
Where are you going?
跟我们一起聚聚吧
Hang out with us.
有什么问题吗？
What's the problem?
你真漂亮
You're pretty.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
说真的 ，你应该...
Seriously, you should...
别碰我！
Don't touch me!
上车
Get in the car.
刚刚真的是个很危险的...举动
That was a very dangerous... move.
我应该回去把那些家伙的头拧下来的
I should go back there and rip those guy's heads off.
不，你不可以
No, you shouldn't.
你不知道他们卑鄙下流的脑袋在想什么
You don't know the vile, repulsive things they're thinking.
这并不难猜
It was not hard to guess.
你能说些别的话题... 来分散我的注意力，好让我不调头回去吗？
Can you talk about something else...and distract me so I won't turn around?
你能系上安全带吗？
Can you just put your seatbelt on?
系上你自己的就可以了
Put your own seatbelt on.
你去哪了 ? 我们有留讯息给你
Where were you? We left you messages.
我们有等你，但是肚子饿了，所以我们..
We waited but we were starving, so we...
我很抱歉我耽误了贝拉的晚餐
I'm sorry I kept Bella from dinner.
我们凑巧遇到，然后聊太久了
We just ran into each other and got talking.
我们能理解，我的意思是 ...
we totally understand, I mean...
碰巧，对吗？
That happens, right?
嗯，我们要走了，那么…
Um, we were just leaving so...
贝拉，你要 ...
Bella, you wanna...
我想我该让贝拉吃点东西
I think I should make sure Bella gets something to eat.
我会开车送你回家的
I'll drive you home myself.
那真是...太体贴了
That's so... thoughtful.
对啊，真是贴心
It's really thoughtful, yeah.
对，我该吃点东西
Yeah, I should eat something.
好吧，那就...明天见了
Okay, so... I'll see you tomorrow.
再见...
See you...
好
Okay.
好的，一份蘑菇馄饨
All right, one mushroom ravioli.
谢谢
Thanks.
呃...真的不必帮你点什么吗 ?
So...Are you sure there isn't anything I can get for you?
不用了，谢谢你
No, thank you.
你真的不吃点东西吗?
You're really not gonna eat?
不，我只是在...节食中
No, I'm on a... special diet.
你真的该给我一些解释
You gotta give me some answers.
是的...不...
Yes... No...
你早就知道?
You knew that?
你怎么知道我在哪里的？
How did you know where I was?
我不知道
I didn't.
好吧...
Alright...
别走...
Don't leave...
你在...跟踪我吗 ?
Did you...follow me?
我只是感觉...很想保护你
I feel very... protective of you.
所以你跟踪我了
So you followed me.
我试着与你保持距离 除非你需要我帮助，然后...
I was trying to keep a distance unless you needed my help and then...
接着我听见那些人渣在想的事情...
I heard what those low-lives were thinking...
等等
Wait
你说你能听见他们在想什么？
You say you heard what they were thinking?
那是什么...你会读人的心思..
So what...You read minds...
我能读这屋子里每个人的心思 除了你之外
I can read every mind in this room apart from yours.
钱...性...
Money...Sex...
Money... Sex...
猫
Cat.
然后你...完全没有
And then you... Nothing.
那让我很有挫折感
It's very frustrating.
我算不正常吗 ?
There's something wrong with me?
我说我能读心，而你却说你不正常
I tell you I can read minds and you think there's something wrong with you.
怎么了?
What is it?
我已没有... 能力... 再和你保持距离了
I don't have...the strength...to stay away from you anymore.
那就不要
Then don't.
好了，我觉得我够暖和了
Okay, I think I'm warm enough now.
你的手很冰
Your hand is so cold.
哇!怎么回事？
Whoa! What is going on?
我爸的车还在这，你能开进去吗 ?
My dad's still here.Can you pull in?
我爸的车也在这
It's my father's car in there.
他在这做什么？
What is he doing here?
卡莱尔，发生甚么事了?
Carlisle, what's going on?
我刚验完尸
I just examined the body.
他死了？
He died?
怎么会？
How?
被野兽袭击
Animal attack.
贝拉
Bella
你该进去里面
you should go inside.
维隆是你父亲的朋友
Waylon was your father's friend.
好的
Okay
呃，等会儿见
Um, I'll see you later.
嘿 ...
Hey...
嘿
Hey.
爸爸，我很难过
Dad, I'm really sorry.
别担心，我们会查出真凶的
Don't worry, we're gonna find this thing.
我要你随身携带这个
I want you to carry this with you.
这能让你老爸安心点
It would give your old man some peace of mind.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
你有令人难以置信的速度 而且强而有力
You're impossibly fast and strong.
你的皮肤苍白且寒冷如冰
Your skin is pale white and ice cold.
你的眼睛会变色...
Your eyes change color...
有时候你的说话的方式像是... 就像你来自不同的年代
And sometimes you speak like...like you're from a different time.
你不吃也不喝任何东西
You never eat or drink anything.
你从不出现在阳光下
You don't go out in the sunlight.
你几岁了 ?
How old are you?
17岁
Seventeen.
17岁多久了？
How long have you been seventeen?
有一段时间了
A while.
我知道你是什么了
I know what you are.
说出来
Say it.
说啊
Say it!
吸血鬼
Vampire.
你害怕吗？
Are you afraid?
不
No.
那问我一个最基本的问题
Then ask me the most basic question
你不会伤害我的
You won't hurt me.
我们要去哪？
Where are we going?
到山顶上，没有云雾垄罩的地方
Up the mountain, out of the cloud bag.
你必须看看我在阳光下的样子
You need to see what I look like in the sunlight.
这就是为何我们不在阳光下暴露的原因
This is why we don't show ourselves in sunlight.
人们会发现我们是异类
People would know we're different.
这就是真正的我
This is what I am.
看起来像钻石似的...
It's like diamonds...
你好美
You're beautiful.
美？这可是杀人魔的皮肤呢，贝拉
Beautiful?This is the skin of a killer, Bella.
我就是一个杀人魔
I'm a killer.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
那是因为你只相信谎言 ...
That's because you believe the lie...
那都是骗人的
It's camouflage.
我是世界上最危险的掠食者
I'm the world's most dangerous predator.
我所有的一切都在引诱你过来
Everything about me invites you in.
我的声音，容貌 ...甚至我的气味
My voice, my face... Even my smell.
我天生就是个掠杀者
I'm designed to kill.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我以前杀过人
I've killed people before.
那没关系
It doesn't matter.
我曾想过要杀了你
I wanted to kill you.
我一生从未如此渴望的想要一个人的血
I've never wanted a human's blood so much in my life.
我信任你
I trust you.
别这么想
Don't.
我就在这，我相信你
I'm here, I trust you.
我的家族，我们跟同类有所不同
My family, we're different from others of our kind.
我们只猎杀动物
We only hunt animals.
我们已经学会控制身体的欲望
We've learned to control our thirst.
至于你 ...你的气息 ... 对我来说像是毒品
As to you... Your scent...is like a drug to me.
我到现在还不知道是否控制得了自己
I still don't know if I can control myself.
我知道你可以的
I know you can.
我读不到你的心
I can't read your mind,
你得告诉我你现在在想什么
you have to tell me what you're thinking.
现在我害怕了
Now I'm afraid.
很好
Good.
我不是害怕你...
I'm not afraid of you...
我只是害怕失去你
I'm only afraid of losing you.
你不知道我等了你多久
You don't know how long I've waited for you.
就这样，狮子爱上了羔羊
And so the lion fell in love with the lamb.
多蠢的羔羊
What a stupid lamb.
多病态又自虐的狮子
What a sick, masochistic lion.
首先，爱德华是个吸血鬼
First, Edward was a vampire.
第三 我已经毫无保留地，无可救药地爱上了他
And third,I was unconditionally and irrevocably in love with him.
蒙地卡罗？这是我们舞会的主题？
Monte Carlo? That's our Prom theme?
嗯，赌博...燕尾服...
Uhu, gambling...Tuxedos...
还有庞德 ...詹姆士庞德
And Bond...James Bond.
喔...我的...天啊
Oh...My...God
你知道吗，大家都开始盯着我们看...
You know, everybody's staring...
那个人不是...
Not that guy...
反正我已经打破所有规矩了
I'm breaking all the rules now anyway.
那你这样已经多久了？
So, how long have you been like this?
从1918年起...
Since 1918...
那是什么样的感觉 ?
What was it like?
那毒液...让人很难忍受
The venom ...was excruciating
但卡莱尔要承受更多的痛苦与挣扎
But what Carlisle did was much harder.
我们之中没几个能控制得那么好
Not many of us have the restraint to do that.
但是，他不是只需要...咬吗 ?
But didn't he just have to... bite?
不完全是
Not exactly.
不，那不是唯一的原因
No, that's not the only reason.
我不想变成一个怪物
I don't want to be a monster.
我们家族自认为是素食者
My family, we think of ourselves as vegetarians.
因为我们是靠动物的血维生的
Cause we only survive on the blood of animals.
就像是人类只靠奶糖过活一样
It's...like a human only living on toffee.
是不是有其它的吸血鬼杀了维隆 ?
Was it other vampires that killed Waylon?
我们时常会碰巧遇到他们
We run into them from time to time.
你家族的人也和你一样会读心术吗 ?
Can the rest of your family read people's minds like you can?
不，只有我可以
No. That's just me.
不过艾莉丝能预见未来
But Alice can see the future.
我打赌她看见我来了
I bet she saw me coming.
艾莉丝的预知是有主观性的
Alice's vision is subjective.
我的意思是，未来随时会改变的
I mean, the future can always change.
天啊...你的行为能像个人一样吗 ?
God...can you act human?
我的意思是我还有邻居
I mean, I've got neighbors.
我明天想要带你去我家
I'm gonna take you to my place tomorrow.
谢了
Thanks.
等等，是要去见你家人吗 ?
Wait, with your family?
对
Yeah.
万一他们不喜欢我怎么办？
What if they don't like me?
我很高兴我逗你笑了
I'm glad I amuse you.
怎么了?
What is it?
这说来复杂
A complication.
我明天来接你
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
嘿!来拜访你的卡车吗？
Hey! Come to visit your truck?
看起来不错嘛
Looks good.
是啊
Yeah.
其实我们是来拜访你家电视的
Actually, we came to visit your flat-screen.
本季水手队的首场比赛阿，非看不可
First Mariners game of the season.
再加上雅各布老是嚷着要见你
Plus, Jacob here keeps bugging me about seeing you again.
好的，爸....谢了
Great, dad...Thanks.
诚实点吧，孩子
Just keeping it real, son.
麦芽白酒
Pale Ale.
干的好，警长
Well done, Chief.
克尔渥特哈利家传的美味炸鱼
Harry Clearwater's homemade fish fry.
非常好
Good.
维隆的案子有什么进展吗？
Any luck with that Waylon case?
我从不这么认为
I never thought it was.
你在保留区放话了没，呃 ?
You spread the word out at the rez, huh?
让孩子们远离森林
Keep the kids out of the woods.
不希望再有任何人受伤了，对吧？
Don't want no one else getting hurt, do we?
真是令人难以置信
This is incredible.
这地方宽敞又明亮，你知道的
It's so white and open, you know.
这是我们唯一不必躲藏的地方
This is the one place we don't have to hide.
我吩咐过他们别如此大费周章的
I told them not to do this.
加点橄榄油在这个平底锅上
You add a little of olive oil to a non-stick saut's pan.
她是意大利人？
Is she even Italian?
她的名字叫贝拉
Her name is Bella.
我肯定不管吃什么她都会喜欢的
I'm sure she'll love it no matter what.
深呼吸看看
Get a whiff of that
有人类来啰
Here comes the human.
贝拉 ! 我们为了你做意大利料理呢
Bella! We're making Italiano for you.
哦!
Oh!
贝拉，这是艾丝蜜
Bella, this is Esme.
我把她当作是亲妈妈
My mother for all intents and purposes.
你让我们第一次有机会用到厨房
You've given us an excuse to use the kitchen for the first time.
我想你一定饿了吧
I hope you're hungry.
她吃过了
She already ate.
好极了！
Perfect!
呃，这实在...
Yeah, it's just...
我...我知道你们不吃这些...
I...I know you guys don't eat...
当然啰，你真善解人意
Of course, it's very considerate of you.
好吧，让我们假装这样对我们大家都很安全
Yeah, let's just keep pretending like this isn't dangerous for all of us.
我绝不会告诉任何人的
I would never tell anybody anything
对，好吧，但问题是...
Yeah, well, the problem is...
你们两个现在是公开的了，所以...
You two have become public now, so...
艾密特 !
Emmett!
不，她必须明白
No,she should know.
如果你们结局不好，整个家族都会被牵连的
The entire family will be implicated if this ends badly.
最坏的结果就是...
Badly as in...
我...我变成食物
I...I become the meal.
嗨，贝拉 !
Hi, Bella!
我是艾莉丝
I'm Alice.
嗨
Hi.
哦，你闻起来确实很不错
Oh, you do smell good.
抱歉，贾斯柏是最后加入的素食者
Sorry, Jasper's our newest vegetarian.
对他来说还有点难适应
It's a little difficult for him.
很荣幸认识你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
没问题的，贾斯柏，你不会伤害她的
It's okay, Jasper. You won't hurt her.
好吧...
Alright...
我带你去四处参观一下吧
I'm gonna take you on a tour of the rest of the house.
我们待会儿见
I'll see you soon.
好的
Okay.
很可爱呢
Cute
看来进展的不错
I think that went well.
把这里弄干净
Clean this up.
马上！
Now!
你应该也跟我一样觉得不自在吧？
Was that as weird for you as it was for me?
我不知道
I don't know.
毕业帽？
Graduation caps?
对
Yeah,
这是私下的玩笑
it's a private joke.
我们入学很多次
We matriculate a lot.
那有点可怜
That's kind of miserable.
我指的是，不断的重复念高中
I mean, repeating High School over and over.
来吧
Come on.
嗯，对，这就是我的房间
Um, yeah.This is my room.
没有床？
No bed?
我不睡觉的
I don't sleep.
好吧...
Okay...
你都听些什么音乐 ?
What were you listening to?
对
Yeah.
怎么了？
What?
我不会跳舞
I can't dance.
我可不怕你
I'm not scared of you.
你最好抓紧了，蜘蛛猴
You better hold on tight, spider monkey.
你相信我吗？
Do you trust me?
理论上是的
In theory.
那就闭上眼睛
Then close your eyes.
什么?
What?
这不像真的
This isn't real.
这么美的地方根本不可能存在的
This kind of stuff just doesn't exist.
在我的世界里是存在的
It does in my world.
哇!别动
Whoa! Hold on.
是人的脚印
It's human.
亚历桑纳 ! 呦，怎么回事 ?
Arizona! Yo, what's happening?
是的
Yes.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like it,
我意思是...他看你的眼神好像要吃掉你一样
I mean...He looks at you like you're something to eat
抱歉我来晚了，生物课作业
I'm sorry I'm late. Biology Projects.
我帮你点了猪肉色拉
I ordered you the Spam Salad.
下次你也该点点看这个
You should order one for yourself next time.
牛排加双蛋
Cup-egg on a steak
嘿，我可壮的跟马一样呢
Hey, I'm as healthy as a horse.
今天在银溪沿岸有没有找到什么线索？
Did you find anything down by Creek Silver today?
有，我们发现一个像是人类的赤脚足迹
Yeah, We found a bare human footprint.
好
Okay
没问题吧？
Okay?
你朋友似乎在和你打招呼呢
Looks like your friends are flagging you.
没事的，如果你想去就去吧
It's okay. If you wanna go, join them.
反正我本来就想早点走
I was gonna try to leave early anyway.
我也是
Me too.
看来纽顿家的孩子对你很友善
Looks like the Newton boy's got a big smile for you.
是啊，他人还不错
Yeah, he's a good buddy.
你对哪一个有兴趣 ?
Anybody you're interested?
爸，我们一定要谈男孩子吗 ?
Dad, we're gonna talk about boys?
你应该多去接触人群的
You should be around people.
我不介意一个人啊
I don't mind being alone.
我想这点是老爸遗传给我的
I guess I'm kind of like my dad in that way.
那么，球赛进行的怎么样了？
So, how's all the baseball stuff going?
喔，费尔似乎很努力
Oh, Phil's working so hard.
你会喜欢杰克逊维尔州的，宝贝
You'd like Jacksonville, baby.
是吗？
Yeah?
我真的很喜欢福克斯的人
I'm really liking Forks.
什么？
What?
福克斯镇征服我了
Forks is getting to me.
是不是和哪个男孩有关？
Could a guy have anything to do with that?
对...
Yeah...
我就知道!都说给我听吧，他是什么样的？运动员？
I knew it! Tell me everything.What is he? A jock?
玩音乐的？我打赌他一定很聪明，对吧？
Indie? I bet he's smart.Is he smart?
妈，我晚点再跟你聊，好吗 ?
Mom, can I talk to you later?
哎哟，我们正讨论男孩子呢!
Come on, we gotta talk boys!
你怎么进来的？
How did you get in here?
从窗户
The window.
你经常这么做？
Do you do that a lot?
几个月前才开始的而已
Just the past couple months.
我喜欢看你睡觉的样子
I like watching you sleep.
这个，呃...
It's, um...
那对我来说很有吸引力
Kind of fascinating to me.
呃，我只想试试看一件事...
Um, I just want to try one thing...
只要别动就好
Stay very still.
别动...
Don't move...
停！
Stop!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
对...真希望我也能这么说
Yeah... I wish I could say the same.
我不能因为你而失控
I can never lose control with you.
嘿，别走
Hey, don't go.
谢谢
Thanks.
我跟爱德华 库伦在约会
I have a date with Edward Cullen.
他对你来说有点老，不是吗？
He's a little old for you, isn't he?
不会啊，我们俩都是高中生
No.he's a junior, I'm a junior.
我以为你喜欢库伦家的人
I thought you liked the Cullens.
我以为你不会喜欢镇上的男孩
I thought you didn't like any of the boys in town.
他现在就在门外
He's right outside.
是啊，他想要与你见面...正式的
Yeah, he wanted to meet you...Officially.
好啊
Alright
带他来吧
Bring him in.
你会对他友善点吗？
Could you be nice?
他对我很重要
He is important.
史旺警长
Chief Swan
我想正式介绍我自己，我是爱德华．库伦
I want to formally introduce myself. I'm Edward Cullen.
嗨，爱德华
Hi, Edward.
贝拉今晚不会太晚回家的
Bella won't be out too late tonight.
她只是与我的家人玩棒球
She's just gonna play baseball with my family.
棒球？
Baseball?
是的，长官，这是预订的行程
Yes sir, that's the plan.
贝拉要玩棒球 ?
Bella's gonna play baseball?
好吧，祝你好运了
Well, good luck with that.
我会照顾她的，我保证
I'll take good care of her, I promise.
你还拿着我给你的防狼喷雾剂吧？
You still got that pepper spray?
是的，爸爸
Yeah, dad.
什么时候吸血鬼也喜欢棒球了？
Since when do vampires like baseball?
呃，那是美式消遣
Well, it's the American pastime.
而且刚好有个大雷雨要来了
And there's a thunderstorm coming.
那是我们唯一可以玩的时候
It's the only time we can play.
你会知道原因的
You'll see why.
我很高兴你能来，因为我们需要一个裁判
I'm glad you're here,we need an umpire.
她觉得我们作弊
She thinks we cheat.
我知道你会作弊
I know you cheat.
好的
Okay.
开始了
It's time
好吧，现在我知道为何你们需要打雷了
Okay, now I see why you need the thunder.
那应该是个全垒打，对吧？
That's gonna be a homerun, right?
爱德华速度很快
Edward's very fast.
你出局了
You're out.
出局!哦！
Out! Whoo!
宝贝，别这样!只是场游戏罢了
Babe, come on! It's just a game.
很好，孩子
Nice, kid.
停！
Stop!
他们本来要离开，但却听见了我们
They were leaving, then they heard us.
太迟了
It's too late.
把你的头发放下来
Get your hair up.
我从很远就能闻到她的气味了
I could smell her from across the field.
我真不该带你来这里的，很对不起...
I shouldn't have brought you here.I'm so sorry...
怎么了？
What?
站在我后面别出声
Just be quiet and stand behind me.
谢谢
Thank you.
我叫劳伦特
I'm Laurent
这是维多莉亚
And this is Victoria
还有詹姆斯
And James.
我叫卡莱尔
I'm Carlisle
这是我的家人
This is my family.
你们好
Hello.
我怕你们的捕猎活动会造成我们的困扰
I'm afraid your hunting activities have caused something of a mess for us.
很抱歉
Our apologies.
我们不知道这个区域已经被认领了
We didn't realize the territory had been claimed.
是的，呃...我们在附近有个固定住所
Yes, well...We maintain a permanent residence nearby.
真的吗？
Really?
好吧，我们不会再让你们困扰了
Well, we won't be a problem anymore.
我们只是路过这里而已
We were just passing through.
人类在追捕我们，但我们误导他们去东边了
The humans were tracking us but we lead them east.
你们会安全的
You should be safe.
好极了
Excellent.
那么..
So...
你们可以再加三个球员吗？
Could you use three more players?
喔，别这样，不过是场游戏而已
Oh, come on. Just one game.
当然 有何不可呢？
Sure,why not?
我们有三位正好要离开
Three of us were leaving.
你们可以补上他们的位置
You can take their place.
你们先投吧
You go first.
我是个擅长投诡异曲球的人
I'm the one with the wicked curve-ball.
嗯，我认为我们应付的来
Well, I think we can handle that.
我们走着瞧...
We shall see...
你们带了点心
You brought a snack.
你是人类？
You're human?
这个女孩和我们是一起的
The girl is with us.
我想你们最好还是离开吧
I think it best if you leave.
我知道游戏结束了
I can see the game is over.
我们现在就走
We'll go now.
詹姆斯
James.
带贝拉离开这里...快走
Get Bella out of here...Go.
好啦，我知道了! 我知道了! 我没事
Okay, I've got it! I've got it! I'm alright.
什么 ? 詹姆斯要追杀我 ?
What? Now James is coming after me?
听我说，詹姆斯是个追踪者
Listen to me, James is a tracker.
我在场地的反应刺激了他
My reaction at the field set him off.
我让他觉得这是他生平最刺激的游戏
I just made this his most exciting game ever.
他不会就此罢手的
He's never gonna stop.
我们该怎么办 ?
What should we do?
我们必须杀了他
We have to kill him.
把他撕成一片片的，然后烧掉
Rip him apart and burn the pieces.
我们要去哪？
Where are we going?
离开福克斯
Away from Forks.
我们搭渡轮去温哥华
We'll get a ferry to Vancouver.
你不能回家
You can't go home.
他会从那里追踪你的气味
He's just gonna trace your scent there.
那里将是他观察的首要地点
It's the first place he's gonna look.
但我爸爸在那
But my dad is there.
那不重要！
It doesn't matter!
不，那有关系的！他可能会因为我们而死
Yes, it does!He could get killed because of us.
让我先带你离开这里，好吗 ?
Just let me get you out of here first, alright?
那是我爸爸!我们必须回去
It's my dad! We have to go back.
我们得想办法引开他
We'll figure how to lead the tracker
爱德华，我说了别管我！
Edward, I said leave me alone!
贝拉，别这样，拜托...
Bella, don't do this, please...
嘿...嘿 ! 嘿 !
Hey...Hey! hey!
贝拉，怎么回事 ?
Bella, what's going on?
我要离开这里
I just gotta get out of here.
现在就走！
I'm leaving..Now!
贝拉 ?
Bella?
我要怎么对他说 ?
What am I gonna say to him?
我不能伤害他
I can't hurt him.
贝拉，发生什么事了 ?
Bella, what's going on?
你必须这么做
You'll just have to.
我在卡车里等你
I'll be down at the truck.
他伤害了你？
Did he hurt you?
不
No
和你分手还是什么？
Break up with you or something?
不，我...是我甩了他
No, I... I broke up with him.
我以为你喜欢他
I thought you liked him.
对，这就是为什么我要走
Yeah, that's just why I have to leave.
我不想这样，我要回家
I don't want this, I have to go home.
家？你妈妈甚至不在凤凰城
Home ? Your mom is not even in Phoenix.
我在路上会打给她
I'll call her from the road.
你没必要现在开车回去
You don't have to drive home right now.
你可以先去睡觉
You can sleep on it.
如果明早你还想走，我可以带你去机场
If you still feel like going in the morning, I'll take you to the airport.
不，我想开车走，这样比较有时间思考
No, I want to drive, it will give more time to think.
你放心，如果我真的累了，我会找个旅馆 我保证
If I get really tired, I'll pull into a motel.I promise.
呃，贝拉，我知道跟我相处很无趣
Look, Bella.I know I'm not that much fun to be around.
但是我可以改的
But I can change that.
我们可以一起做很多事情的
We can do more stuff together.
例如？整天盯着电视看棒球比赛？
Like what ? Like watch baseball on the flatscreen?
每晚一起吃晚饭？牛排和馅饼？
Eat at the dinner every night?Steak and Cobbler?
贝拉，别这样，我只是...想让你留下
Bella, come on. I just... got you back.
是啊，你知道...如果我现在不走 我就会像妈一样永远陷在这里
Yeah, you know... If I don't get out now,I'm just gonna be just stuck here like mom.
你爸爸会原谅你的
Your father's gonna forgive you.
让我来开吧 ?
Why don't you let me drive?
他不会的
He won't.
你没看到他的表情
You should have seen his face.
那是唯一能让你走的方法
It was the only way he'd let you go.
现在先别担心他了，他很安全
Just don't worry about him now.He's safe.
追踪者正在跟着我们
The tracker's following us.
那是艾密特
It's just Emmett.
艾莉丝的车跟在后面
Alice is in the car behind us.
等一下 !
Wait!
他是来警告我们关于詹姆斯的事
He came to warn us About James.
这不是我引起的战争
This isn't my fight
而且我早已厌倦他的游戏了
And I've grown tired of his games.
但他拥有空前的感官能力，绝对是致命性的
But he's got unparalleled senses, absolutely lethal.
三百年来，我从没见过像他那么厉害的
I've never seen anything like him in my three hundred years.
还有那个女的，维多莉亚...绝不要低估了她
And the woman, Victoria...Don't underestimate her.
我以前被迫与同类作战过，很难杀的死对方
I've had to fight our kind before.We're not easy to kill.
但并不是不可能
But not impossible.
我们会把他撕成一片片然后烧了
We'll rip him apart and burn the pieces.
我并不喜好杀死另一种同类
I don't relish the thought of killing another creature.
要是他先杀了我们其中一个呢？
What if he kills one of us first?
我会带贝拉逃到南方，把追踪者引开这里
I'm gonna run Bella south and then lead the tracker away from here.
不，爱德华，詹姆斯知道你不可能离开贝拉
No, Edward. James knows you'd never leave Bella.
他会跟踪你的
He'll follow you.
我和贝拉一起走，贾斯柏和我开车带她南下
I'll go with Bella.Jasper and I will drive her south.
我会保护她的，爱德华
I'll keep her safe, Edward.
你们控制得住自己吗 ?
Can you keep your thoughts to yourself?
是的
Yes.
罗丝莉...艾丝蜜
Rosalie... Esme.
为什么？她和我是什么关系？
Why? What is she to me?
罗丝莉
Rosalie.
贝拉与爱德华现在是情侣
Bella is with Edward.
她现在是我们家族的一份子
She is part of this family now.
而我们永远会保护家人
And we protect our family.
如果发生了什么意外，我发誓...
If anything happens, I swear to God...
不会有事的
Nothing's gonna happen.
我们是七个对付他们两个呢
There's seven of us against two of them.
而且等事情结束后 我就会去接你的
And when everything's done I'm gonna come back and get you.
好的
Yeah.
贝拉，从现在起你就是我的生命了
Bella, you are my life now.
嘿，妈妈，又是我
Hey, mom. It's me again.
我现在不在福克斯，但我没事，过后再跟你解释
I'm not in Forks but everything's okay and I'll explain it later.
罗丝，在树群中作标记
Rose, among the three.
很好
That's good.
怎么了 ? 你看见什么 ?
What is it? What did you see?
被他识破了
He figured it out.
追踪者，他改变路线了
The tracker. He just changed course.
他往哪个方向了，艾莉丝 ?
Where will it take him, Alice?
镜子...一个全是镜子的房间
Mirrors...A room full of mirrors.
艾德华说你看到的不一定是正确的
Edward said the visions weren't always certain.
她看到的过程必须是那个人刚好在那里
She sees the course people are on while they're on it.
如果他们改变主意了，看到的也会变
If they change their minds, the vision changes.
那么，追踪者现在的路线...
So, the course that the tracker's on now is gonna...
你去过？
You've been here?
我小时候在那上过课
I took lessons as a kid.
我去的学校有个这样的拱门
The school I went to had an arch just like that.
你的学校也在凤凰城 ?
Was your school here in Phoenix?
是的
Yeah.
艾德华，你没事吧 ?
Edward, you okay?
罗丝莉和艾丝蜜回到福克斯去保护你爸爸
Rosalie and Esme have gone back to Forks to protect your father.
我马上过去找你
I'm coming to get you.
然后我们一起去别的地方.
Then you and I are gonna go somewhere.
其它人会继续追捕他
And the others will keep hunting.
我会不惜一切代价保护你的安全
I'll do whatever it takes to make you safe.
嘿，妈！我很高兴你收到我的信息了
Hey, mom! I'm glad you got my message.
你在家做什么？
What are you doing home?
贝拉 ! 贝拉! 贝拉 ? 你在哪儿 ?
Bella! Bella! Bella? Where are you?
冷静点，没事的
Calm down, everything's fine.
贝拉 !
Bella!
我晚点再跟你解释...妈，你还好吗 ?
I'll explain everything later...Mom, are you alright?
让维多利亚很简单的就找到了你以前的地址
It was just too easy for Victoria to find your previous address.
你住过的房子还不错
It's a nice house you have here.
我本来就打算好在这等你来的
I was prepared to wait for you.
但是当你妈妈接到一通你爸焦急的电话后就回家来了
But then mom came home after she received a very worried call from your dad.
一切都进展的相当顺利
It all worked out quite well.
等等
Wait
你还有机会救她的
You can still save her.
但是你必须离开你的朋友们
But you're gonna have to get away from your friends.
你能做到吗？
Can you handle that?
我去哪里见你 ?
Where should I meet you?
你以前的芭蕾教室如何 ?
How about your old ballet studio?
我从来都没想过我会怎么死
I'd never given much thought to how I would die
但为自己所爱的人而死似乎是个不错的选择
But dying in the place of someone I love seems like a good way to go.
我不会因为这个让我自己面对死亡的决定而感到后悔
I can't bring myself to regret the decisions that brought me face to face with dead.
妈妈
Mom
贝拉?  妈！
Bella?  Mom!
你在这里做什么 ?
What are you doing in here?
每个人都取笑我
Everyone makes fun of me.
你是个很棒的舞者
You are a wonderful dancer.
妈妈，我糟透了
Mom, I suck!
你一点都不糟糕
You do not suck.
这段是我最喜欢的部分
That's my favorite part.
你是个固执的孩子，不是吗？
You were a stubborn child, weren't you?
她根本不在这里
She's not even here
所以...为了有更多的娱乐效果 我们来拍一点我们在一起的影片
so... To make things more entertaining,we are gonna make a little film of our time together.
我从你家里带来这个，希望你别介意
I borrowed this from your house.I hope you don't mind.
好的...
Okay...
然后 ....开始 !
And...Action!
这会让艾德华心碎的
That will break Edward's little heart.
艾德华跟这事无关 !
Edward has nothing to do with this!
他的愤怒会让这场游戏更加有趣.
His rage will leave for more interesting sporthings.
我们继续吧
And let's continue.
真美...非常有视觉动感
Beautiful... Very visually dynamic.
我真是选对了舞台
I chose my stage well.
他没勇气改造你真是太糟糕了
It's too bad he didn't have the strength to turn you.
这可真是残忍
It's cruel, really.
跟他说为你报仇吧
Tell him to avenge you.
告诉他为你报仇！说！
Tell him to avenge you! Tell him!
艾德华，不要 !
Edward, don't!
告诉他！
Tell him!
你落单了...因为你比其它人都快
You're alone...cause you're faster than the others.
我强到能杀了你
I'm strong enough to kill you.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
贝拉，贝拉 ! 没事了
Bella, Bella! It's okay.
够了！别失去了你的本性
Enough! Remember who you are.
贝拉需要你
Bella needs you.
哦，天啊
Oh God.
卡莱尔 ! 这血...
Carlisle! The blood...
你的兄弟们会解决他的
Your brothers will take care of it.
用地上的木板生火
Start the fire with the floor boards.
艾莉丝 !
Alice!
艾莉丝，快
Alice, go.
不，不，我的手...烧起来了!
No, no, my hand... Is burning!
那是毒液的关系
It's the venom.
为了不让她转化，你必须做个选择
You have to make a choice to prevent the change happen.
不...
No...
不！
No!
这会发生的，艾德华，我预见到了
It's gonna happen, Edward. I've seen it.
不一定非要这样做
It doesn't have to be that way.
她还在出血..，艾莉丝
She's still hemorrhaging...Alice
把你的皮带给我当止血带
Make me a tourniquet with your belt.
卡莱尔，我还有其它选择吗 ?
Carlisle, what's my other option?
把它绑在我的手上
Tie it above my hands.
卡莱尔 !
Carlisle!
快
Go.
试着把毒液吸出来
To try to suck the venom out.
你知道我可能没办法停下来的
You know I won't be able to stop.
那就用你的意志力...去阻止
Then find the will...To stop.
她没几分钟可活了
She only has minutes left.
我不会让你离开我的，贝拉
I can't make you go away, Bella.
但我会让痛苦离开你的
But I'll make it go away.
艾德华，停下来 !
Edward, stop!
血已经干净了，再下去你会杀死她的
The blood is clean, you're killing her.
爱德华，停下来 !
Edward, stop!
快停下来，意志力要坚定
Stop. Find the will.
死亡是那么安详... 简单...
Dead is peaceful... Easy...
活着却是如此困难
Life is harder.
贝拉 ?
Bella?
宝贝？
Baby?
贝拉 ?
Bella?
妈妈...
Mom...
嘿...
Hey...
他在哪里 ? 在哪...爱德华在哪儿 ?
Where is he? Where's... Where is Edward?
他睡着了
He's asleep.
他一直没离开过
He never leaves.
而你爸爸在楼下的餐厅
And your dad is down at the cafeteria.
发生了甚么事 ?
What happened?
呃，你跌倒的时候，摔断了腿
Well, when you fell you broke your leg.
你一点都不记得了吗？
You don't remember any of this, do you?
艾德华和他父亲 试着要劝你回去福克斯
Edward came down with his dad to try to convince to come back to Forks.
所以你去他们饭店时，就这么滑倒了... 摔下两段楼梯
So you went over to their hotel and you tripped...and fell down two flights of stairs.
是的，那听起来蛮像我的
Yeah, it sounds like me.
哦，亲爱的，我很抱歉
Oh, honey. I'm so sorry.
是费尔
It's Phil.
他很担心你
He's so worried about you.
你会发简讯了?
You're texting?
是啊，终于会了
Finally, yeah.
我要他留在佛罗里达
I told him to stay down in Florida.
哦，亲爱的，你会喜欢杰克逊维尔州的
Oh, honey. You are gonna love Jacksonville.
那里每天都阳光明媚
It's sunny everyday day.
而且我们找到了一间很可爱的房子
And we found the cutest little house
不，妈妈，我还是想住在福克斯镇
No, Mom. I still wanna live in Forks.
什么？
What?
我想住在福克斯
I wanna live in Forks.
呃，好吧，我们再说吧
Well, okay. We'll talk about it.
你介意去找一下爸爸吗？
Do you mind getting dad?
我有话要跟他说，跟他道歉
I have to talk to him. Apologize.
好的，宝贝，我去叫他
Okay, baby.I'll go get him.
我也会找护士过来的，好吗 ?
And I'll go get a nurse, okay?
好的
Okay.
发生了什么事 ? 詹姆斯哪里去了 ?
What happened? Where is James?
都是因为你我才能活着
I'm alive because of you.
不，你是因为我才沦落成这样的
No, you're in here because of me.
最糟糕的是... 我以为我没办法停止
The worst part of it was...I thought I wasn't gonna be able to stop.
可是你停下来了
You did stop.
贝拉，你应该去杰克森维尔的 这样我就不会再伤害你了
Bella, you gotta go to Jacksonville,so I can't hurt you anymore.
什么？
What?
不，不！
No, no!
我...我不能离开你.
I...I can't just leave you.
我知道了
I know.
我会在这的
I'm here.
好了，你不准再对我说那种话了
Okay. You just can't just say stuff like that to me.
哪里还有...我的容身之处呢？
Where else...am I gonna go?
艾莉丝借给我的礼服
Alice lent me the dress.
我会照顾她的，史旺警长
I'll take care of her, Chief Swan.
呃，这句话好像有听你说过
Uhu. I've heard that before.
嘿，贝拉
Hey, Bells.
我在你包包里放了一罐新的防狼喷雾剂
I put a new can of Pepper spray on your bag.
爸爸...
Dad...
还有 呃..
And, um..
你看起来真的好美
You look beautiful.
谢谢
Thanks
再见
See you
贝拉
Bella
雅各布，嘿 ！
Jacob,hey!
你也是
You too
你是来舞会捣乱的？
Are you crashing the prom or something?
还是和舞伴一起来的？
Did you come with a date?
不
No.
我爸付钱让我来跟你说话
My dad paid me to come talk to you.
说来听听
Let's hear it.
先别生气，好吗？
Just don't get mad, okay?
他希望你跟男朋友分手
He wants you to break up with your boyfriend.
喔，让我帮你吧
Oh, let me help you.
雅各布
Jacob
我会常来看你的，贝拉
I guess I'll see you around, Bella.
我只离开你两分钟，狼人就趁虚而入了
I leave you alone for two minutes and the wolves descend.
笑一个
Smile.
哇喔 ! 你还真想害死我呢
Wow! You are really trying to kill me.
舞会是进行的一个重要仪式
Prom is an important rite of passage.
我不希望你错过任何过程
I don't want you to miss anything.
贝拉!
Bella!
想出去吗？
You wanna go?
好的
Yeah.
好的...慢慢地...
Alright... Slowing it down...
跳舞吗？
Shall we?
你是说真的吗
You're serious?
哦，有何不可呢？
Oh, why not?
瞧？你正在跳舞呢
See? You're dancing.
在舞会上...
At Prom...
爱德华，你为什么救我 ?
Edward, why did you save me?
假如当时你让毒液扩散...现在我就和你一样了
If you just had let the venom spread...I could be like you right now.
你不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you're saying.
你不会想要这样的
You don't want this.
我不会帮你结束生命的
I'm not gonna end your life for you.
我已经在..慢慢死亡了
I'm dying...Already.
它本来就是会这样的
That's the way it's supposed to be.
艾莉丝说她看到我像你一样，我有听她说了
Alice said that she saw me like you.I heard her.
她预见的变了
Her visions change.
是啊， 某一天有人抉择了
Yeah, but someday people decide.
我已经决定了
I've decided.
这就是你梦到的吗？
Is that what you dream about?
变成一个怪物？
Becoming a monster?
我梦到和你永远在一起
I dream about being with you forever.
永远...
Forever...
你现在准备好了吗？
Are you ready right now?
是的
Yes.
跟我快乐度过一生难道还不够吗 ?
Is it not enough just to have a long and happy life with me?
是的
Yeah.
就现在
For now.
今晚没人会投降的
No one will surrender tonight.
我也不会让步的
But I won't give in.
我知道我要的是什么
I know what I want.